In your opinion, what
characteristics are necessary to do
your job well?
It takes passion and discipline and
of course also a certain ability to
resist stress.
Even after you've been working at this company for 20 years
, does it still stress you out?
And it's a job that [laughter] takes your
soul and body.  That is, the responsibility
is not only for customers, but also for
employees.  I often hear "But who
makes you do it?"  Or do they criticize you for
sacrificing other things?  It's important to know
why you do it, and I believe that
responsibility towards society and towards its
employees and their families
is one of the most important things. If there
aren't people—I don't consider myself
above or a special person—
if there aren't people who take
responsibility for doing and
also thinking about the common good, we'll really
struggle in the future.  This is just the way
of doing business.